mexgrocer.com 2002-12-04

# MexGrocer.com online grocery store for mexican food products and mexican recipes

Privacy Policy Overview MexGrocer.com is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its customers. We have written this privacy policy to inform you of the specific information that we collect from you, how we use this information, and what options you have in sharing this information with us when you visit our site. Protecting your privacy is a significant part of MexGrocer.com's commitment to providing you with a high quality shopping experience.

This confirms that MexGrocer.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe certifies this website’s online gathering and dissemination of information and privacy practices. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our Customer Service Department through any method desired at the end of this policy. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog_intro.html) directly. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

Information Collection and Use ** **

MexGrocer.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. MexGrocer.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Registration ** **

In order to access all functionalities on this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information, and unique identifiers, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.

Order ** **

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. MexGrocer does not process credit card transactions directly; we use VeriSign, Inc., which is a third party authority in trusted modular payment solutions and security systems on the Internet.

Corrections/Updating Personal Information

At any time, members of MexGrocer.com can verify that the information we have about you is accurate by clicking on the "My Account" button to review your personal data. If anything is incorrect or out of date, you are able to make any changes in this area. You will receive an email confirmation with any changes or corrections you have done to your account. Please know that for your security, this area of the site is password protected so even if you have "turned on" the autologin feature, a username and password will still be required to access and change information in your account.

Cookies ** **

MexGrocer will store a persistent cookie so that you may retrieve the products in your shopping cart with no need to go through re-choosing all the categories again. This website's cookies are not tied to any personally identifiable information. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to process through our shopping area. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

Affiliate Programs

We use Commission Junction to run our affiliate program ~~s~~ for advertising purposes to increase MexGrocer’s brand awareness and the store’s existence to larger communities of websites. When a company signs up for an Affiliate Program (apply ONLY to corporations) within the MexGrocer website, the information is collected and stored  by Commission Junction. The usage of this cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information.

Log Files ** **

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Sharing 

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. MexGrocer will share with Univision Online some or all of the personal data collected (i.e. name, email, order information, etc.) from this site ONLY for end-users accessing this site through the [www.Univision.com](http://www.univision.com/) portal, to be used in accordance with Univision's [privacy policy](http://www.univision.com/content/content.jhtml?cid=72057).

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Links ** **

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that MexGrocer.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by MexGrocer.com.

Newsletter ** **

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

Refer-A-Friend 

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. MexGrocer.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. MexGrocer.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact MexGrocer.com at info@mexgrocer.com to request the removal of this information from their database.

Security ** **

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or contact information), that information is encrypted and is protected with 128 bit encryption software from VeriSign - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [VeriSign](http://www.verisign.com/).

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to info@mexgrocer.com.

Supplementation of Information ** **

In order for this website to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our partners, to create a personalized user profile. Customers may have the option to answer a simple survey at the end of the ordering process with BizRate.com, this evaluation of our store will serve as a future testimonial recommendation for other customers to review. In accordance with this survey, we recommend our customers to read BizRate.com's Privacy Policy before submitting their feedback.

Special Offers ** **

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

Administrative Email Communications

You will receive administrative emails that are related to the primary usage of our service. You may not opt-out of administrative emails. These administrative emails will not have any marketing, promotional or advertising material(s) in them.

Choice/Opt-out 

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to “REMOVE” in the subject line in the email sent out or email us at [info@mexgrocer.com](mailto:info@mexgrocer.com) and let us know that you want to opt-out of further newsletter communications. You may also edit your account under the “My Account” tab at the top of the website, login and click to modify your account. There, you will be able to select to not receive the newsletter any more by selecting “NO” in the designated field.

Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will prominently post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Our Guarantee

We are so confident about the security of our site that we back every purchase with this guarantee: If using your credit card on our site results in subsequent unauthorized use of your card, we'll cover your liability up to $50. The unauthorized use must have resulted from giving your credit card information to MexGrocer.com - not from fault of your own. Our guarantee applies only if your credit card information was given to us over the MexGrocer.com secure server.

If you discover unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify MexGrocer.com of the problem in writing (by email or letter) within 24 hours of discovery. You must also notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. We limit our Safe Shopping Guarantee to $50 because your credit card provider likely will either cover the unauthorized charges altogether, or limit your liability to $50 or less. Your card user agreement will have the details.

What Else Should I Know About My Privacy?

Ultimately, you are held responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords. Indeed, you should even be careful about giving your password to someone at MexGrocer.com with the presence of other people. Only in an instance when you have initiated the communication with us, is it safe for you to give your password to a MexGrocer.com employee, should that be necessary. You should never give out your MexGrocer password to anyone who contacts you by phone or e-mail, claiming to be a MexGrocer.com employee over the phone or via e-mail. A legitimate MexGrocer employee will never initiate contact with you and then need to ask for your password. Always be careful and responsible.

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

Your **** Feedback

At MexGrocer.com, your privacy is extremely important. If you have any questions about the privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with MexGrocer, please click Contact Us and let us know or write us by mail at: 

**MexGrocer.com LLC  
P.O. BOX 2888  
La Jolla, CA 92038  
USA

Phone (858)459-0577  
Email

  **
